<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Daily Paper Digest</title>
        <link>https://github.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage</link>
        <description>Algorithmically selected papers from 20+ journal feeds, focused on RF systems, cultural heritage conservation, and adjacent topics.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:35:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage/main/web/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <generator>Paper Digest Service</generator>
    <item>
        <title>MVPTransformer: Long-Term Multivariate Time-Series Pattern for Plasma Array-Based Intelligent Protection Against HPM</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</link>
        <description>In this work, we propose a novel time-series modeling approach that integrates multiperspective feature extraction with multihead attention-based information fusion, complemented by an autonomous thinking strategy (ATS). By conducting case studies and comparing our method with three state-of-the-art time-series models, we validate the superior accuracy and generalizability of our proposed approach. | Score: 6.14</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Naixing Feng;Chunzhi Dong;Jianyuan Fu;Fanghua Zheng;Zhixiang Huang;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adaptive FMCW Radar Interference Suppression via Coupled Range-Doppler Unsupervised Sparse Learning and Reconstruction</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</link>
        <description>The simulation and multiple measured experiments demonstrate the proposed method achieves efficient interference suppression performance. Compared to state-of-the-art methods, the time required to process a single frame of measured data is only 0.0872 s, with the best interference suppression performance. | Score: 5.35</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hao Zhang;Shunjun Wei;Rui Min;Xiang Cai;Shuangqiao Li;Jin Li;Mou Wang;Jun Shi;Guolong Cui;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Training Signal Optimization for Behavioral Modeling and Digital Predistortion of RF Power Amplifiers</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11184392</link>
        <description>The signal is similar to orthogonal frequency-division multiplexing-based signal standards, facilitating its use in training during the regular operation of the wireless transmitter. Experimental validation of this method is also provided in hardware, with a PA using a 100-MHz bandwidth millimeter wave 5G signal. | Score: 5.27</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Jonathan Guimaraes Ribeiro;Yiyue Jiang;Rahul Mushini;Miriam Leeser;John Dooley;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11184392</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>StylizedGS: Controllable Stylization for 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11143957</link>
        <description>Our method achieves high-quality stylization results characterized by faithful brushstrokes and geometric consistency with flexible controls. Extensive experiments across various scenes and styles demonstrate the effectiveness and efficiency of our method concerning both stylization quality and inference speed. | Score: 0.51</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Dingxi Zhang;Yu-Jie Yuan;Zhuoxun Chen;Fang-Lue Zhang;Zhenliang He;Shiguang Shan;Lin Gao;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11143957</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adaptive Temperature-Driven Ternary Contrastive Autoencoder Framework for Hyperspectral Target Detection</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236413</link>
        <description>Hyperspectral target detection (HTD) is a critical task in remote sensing, where numerous deep learning (DL)-based methods have emerged for their powerful ability to extract hierarchical and discriminative features. Experimental results on four real-world benchmark datasets demonstrate that our approach outperforms state-of-the-art methods in terms of detection performance and efficiency. | Score: 5.24</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Jiaojiao Li;Hangyun Liu;Haitao Xu;Chengyuan Wang;Yunsong Li;Qian Du;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236413</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>SSMRadNet : A Sample-wise State-Space Framework for Efficient and Ultra-Light Radar Segmentation and Object Detection</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2511.08769</link>
        <description>The latent representations of a radar frame are decoded to perform segmentation and detection tasks. Comprehensive evaluations on the RADIal dataset show SSMRadNet has 10-33x fewer parameters and 60-88x less computation (GFLOPs) while being 3.7x faster than state-of-the-art transformer and convolution-based radar detectors at competitive performance for segmentation tasks. | Score: 4.63</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Anuab Sen, Mir Sayeed Mohammad, Saibal Mukhopadhyay</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2511.08769</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Leveraging AI multimodal geospatial foundation models for improved near-real-time flood mapping at a global scale</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.02055</link>
        <description>U-Net achieved higher recall than all GFM configurations, though with slightly lower accuracy and precision.
  Our results demonstrate that integrating multimodal optical and SAR data and fine-tuning a GFM can enhance near-real-time flood mapping. This study provides one of the first global-scale evaluations of a GFM for flood segmentation, highlighting both its potential and current limitations for climate adaptation and disaster resilience. | Score: 4.36</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Mirela G. Tulbure, Julio Caineta, Mark Broich, Mollie D. Gaines, Philippe Rufin, Leon-Friedrich Thom</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.02055</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>U-SET: Uncertainty-Aware SAR-to-EO Translation</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</link>
        <description>By leveraging the uncertainty estimation capabilities of deep-learning models, U-SET effectively prioritizes structurally complex and ambiguous regions during training. Comprehensive evaluations on our newly compiled KOMPSAT dataset demonstrate that U-SET achieves state-of-the-art performance, outperforming existing methods across six image quality metrics in both quantitative and qualitative assessments. | Score: 3.56</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Minyoung Jeon;Hyun-Ho Kim;Juheon Park;Doochun Seo;Jaehyup Lee;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>A WaveCluster-Based Robust and Fast Multibaseline InSAR Phase Unwrapping Algorithm</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236427</link>
        <description>However, the MBPU methods still cannot effectively balance PU accuracy and efficiency when processing large-size interferograms. Theoretical analysis and experimental results show that this method has more advantages than the existing MBPU methods in efficiency, accuracy, and adaptability to baseline ratios when processing large-size interferograms. | Score: 3.52</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Zhihui Yuan;Zhengguo Wang;Hanwen Yu;Xuemin Xing;Lifan Zhou;Lifu Chen;Junyi Xu;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236427</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>AR-SMFWI: A Hybrid Artifact Removal and Spatial Multiscale FWI Approach for Common-Offset GPR Data</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236412</link>
        <description>Full waveform inversion (FWI) has shown great potential for high-resolution imaging in ground-penetrating radar (GPR) applications. The proposed approach provides a viable solution for large-scale Co-GPR inversion under limited computational resources and offers new insights for extending FWI to practical GPR imaging scenarios. | Score: nan</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Yu Yang;Xu Bai;Yulong Gao;Hongrui Li;Guanting Liu;</author>
        <category>Random Discovery</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236412</guid>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>