<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Daily Paper Digest</title>
        <link>https://github.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage</link>
        <description>Algorithmically selected papers from 20+ journal feeds, focused on RF systems, cultural heritage conservation, and adjacent topics.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:39:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage/main/web/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <generator>Paper Digest Service</generator>
    <item>
        <title>MVPTransformer: Long-Term Multivariate Time-Series Pattern for Plasma Array-Based Intelligent Protection Against HPM</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</link>
        <description>In this work, we propose a novel time-series modeling approach that integrates multiperspective feature extraction with multihead attention-based information fusion, complemented by an autonomous thinking strategy (ATS). By conducting case studies and comparing our method with three state-of-the-art time-series models, we validate the superior accuracy and generalizability of our proposed approach. | Score: 6.14</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Naixing Feng;Chunzhi Dong;Jianyuan Fu;Fanghua Zheng;Zhixiang Huang;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>ACCOR: Attention-Enhanced Complex-Valued Contrastive Learning for Occluded Object Classification Using mmWave Radar IQ Signals</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.11556</link>
        <description>In this paper, we propose ACCOR, an attention-enhanced complex-valued contrastive learning approach for radar, enabling robust occluded object classification. These results demonstrate the benefits of complex-valued deep learning with attention and contrastive learning for mmWave radar-based occluded object classification in industrial and automated environments. | Score: 5.72</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Stefan H\&quot;agele, Adam Misik, Constantin Patsch, Eckehard Steinbach</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.11556</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Learning-Based Rich Scattering Channel Estimation for U6G FDD XL-MIMO Systems</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11202937</link>
        <description>These conditions pose challenges for downlink channel estimation in frequency division duplex (FDD) mode, as near-field research under U6G remains limited. Numerical results demonstrate that the proposed FDD downlink estimation scheme achieves high accuracy and low overhead, providing a practical solution for near-field XL-MIMO under rich-scattering U6G conditions. | Score: 5.60</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Qianfan Lu;Mengyuan Li;Yu Han;Shi Jin;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11202937</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Efficient 3D Surface Super-Resolution via Normal-Based Multimodal Restoration</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11192222</link>
        <description>This paper introduces an efficient multimodal normal-based 3D surface super-resolution (mn3DSSR) framework, designed to address the challenges of microgeometry enhancement and computational overhead. Extensive experiments conducted on seven benchmark datasets across four different 3D data representations demonstrate that mn3DSSR consistently outperforms state-of-the-art super-resolution methods in terms of restoration accuracy with high computational efficiency. | Score: 1.88</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Miaohui Wang;Yunheng Liu;Wuyuan Xie;Boxin Shi;Jianmin Jiang;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11192222</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adaptive FMCW Radar Interference Suppression via Coupled Range-Doppler Unsupervised Sparse Learning and Reconstruction</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</link>
        <description>The simulation and multiple measured experiments demonstrate the proposed method achieves efficient interference suppression performance. Compared to state-of-the-art methods, the time required to process a single frame of measured data is only 0.0872 s, with the best interference suppression performance. | Score: 5.35</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hao Zhang;Shunjun Wei;Rui Min;Xiang Cai;Shuangqiao Li;Jin Li;Mou Wang;Jun Shi;Guolong Cui;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>RadarFuseNet: Complex-Valued Attention-Based Fusion of IQ Time- and Frequency-Domain Radar Features for Classification Tasks</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.11537</link>
        <description>The proposed method achieves improved performance and robustness compared to standalone complex-valued CNNs. Furthermore, the accuracy for occluded object classification improves from 91.99% using standalone complex-valued CNNs to 94.20% using our proposed approach. | Score: 5.08</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Stefan H\&quot;agele, Adam Misik, Eckehard Steinbach</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.11537</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>U-SET: Uncertainty-Aware SAR-to-EO Translation</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</link>
        <description>By leveraging the uncertainty estimation capabilities of deep-learning models, U-SET effectively prioritizes structurally complex and ambiguous regions during training. Comprehensive evaluations on our newly compiled KOMPSAT dataset demonstrate that U-SET achieves state-of-the-art performance, outperforming existing methods across six image quality metrics in both quantitative and qualitative assessments. | Score: 3.56</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Minyoung Jeon;Hyun-Ho Kim;Juheon Park;Doochun Seo;Jaehyup Lee;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Regularization-Based Coherence Bias Mitigation for InSAR in Low-Coherence Regions</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11272882</link>
        <description>This study proposes a regularization-based approach to reduce coherence estimation bias, especially in areas with few homogeneous samples. Validated using Monte Carlo simulations and real data from 16 TerraSAR-X images of Shanghai, the proposed approach outperforms conventional techniques, achieving lower residual bias and lower estimation standard deviation (STD) across diverse scenes. | Score: 3.49</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hongyu Liang;Xin Gao;Xin Li;Lei Zhang;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11272882</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Wide Field-of-View MMW SISO-SAR Image Reconstruction Based on Curved Linear Array</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11264290</link>
        <description>This letter presents a wide field-of-view (FoV) millimeter-wave array synthetic aperture radar (SAR) imaging system based on curved linear array. Experiments demonstrate high-quality imaging with an extended FoV. | Score: 3.06</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hao Wu;Fengjiao Gan;Xu Chen;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11264290</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>HyperSBINN: A Hypernetwork-Enhanced Systems Biology-Informed Neural Network for Efficient Drug Cardiosafety Assessment</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2408.14266</link>
        <description>arXiv:2408.14266v2 Announce Type: replace-cross 
Abstract: Mathematical modeling in systems toxicology enables a comprehensive understanding of the effects of pharmaceutical substances on cardiac health. This framework represents an advancement in computational modeling, offering a scalable and efficient solution for simulating and understanding complex biological systems. | Score: nan</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Inass Soukarieh, Gerhard Hessler, Herv\&#x27;e Minoux, Marcel Mohr, Friedemann Schmidt, Jan Wenzel, Pierr</author>
        <category>Random Discovery</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2408.14266</guid>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>