<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Daily Paper Digest</title>
        <link>https://github.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage</link>
        <description>Algorithmically selected papers from 20+ journal feeds, focused on RF systems, cultural heritage conservation, and adjacent topics.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:36:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage/main/web/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <generator>Paper Digest Service</generator>
    <item>
        <title>MVPTransformer: Long-Term Multivariate Time-Series Pattern for Plasma Array-Based Intelligent Protection Against HPM</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</link>
        <description>In this work, we propose a novel time-series modeling approach that integrates multiperspective feature extraction with multihead attention-based information fusion, complemented by an autonomous thinking strategy (ATS). By conducting case studies and comparing our method with three state-of-the-art time-series models, we validate the superior accuracy and generalizability of our proposed approach. | Score: 6.14</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Naixing Feng;Chunzhi Dong;Jianyuan Fu;Fanghua Zheng;Zhixiang Huang;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adaptive FMCW Radar Interference Suppression via Coupled Range-Doppler Unsupervised Sparse Learning and Reconstruction</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</link>
        <description>The simulation and multiple measured experiments demonstrate the proposed method achieves efficient interference suppression performance. Compared to state-of-the-art methods, the time required to process a single frame of measured data is only 0.0872 s, with the best interference suppression performance. | Score: 5.35</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hao Zhang;Shunjun Wei;Rui Min;Xiang Cai;Shuangqiao Li;Jin Li;Mou Wang;Jun Shi;Guolong Cui;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>In-Context and Few-Shots Learning for Forecasting Time Series Data based on Large Language Models</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.07705</link>
        <description>More specifically, the paper explores training LLMs through in-context, zero-shot and few-shot learning and forecasting time series data with OpenAI {\tt o4-mini} and Gemini 2.5 Flash Lite, as well as the recent Google&#x27;s Transformer-based TimesFM, a time series-specific foundation model, along with two deep learning models, namely TCN and LSTM networks. Furthermore, OpenAI&#x27;s o4-mini also exhibits a good performance based on Zero Shot learning.
  These findings highlight pre-trained time series foundation models as a promising direction for real-time forecasting, enabling accurate and scalable deployment with minimal model adaptation. | Score: 5.30</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Saroj Gopali, Bipin Chhetri, Deepika Giri, Sima Siami-Namini, Akbar Siami Namin</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.07705</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Efficient 3D Surface Super-Resolution via Normal-Based Multimodal Restoration</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11192222</link>
        <description>This paper introduces an efficient multimodal normal-based 3D surface super-resolution (mn3DSSR) framework, designed to address the challenges of microgeometry enhancement and computational overhead. Extensive experiments conducted on seven benchmark datasets across four different 3D data representations demonstrate that mn3DSSR consistently outperforms state-of-the-art super-resolution methods in terms of restoration accuracy with high computational efficiency. | Score: 1.88</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Miaohui Wang;Yunheng Liu;Wuyuan Xie;Boxin Shi;Jianmin Jiang;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11192222</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>SpectraIrisPAD: Leveraging Vision Foundation Models for Spectrally Conditioned Multispectral Iris Presentation Attack Detection</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.06103</link>
        <description>However, its growing deployment in real-world applications raises significant concerns regarding its vulnerability to Presentation Attacks (PAs). SpectraIrisPAD consistently outperforms several state-of-the-art baselines across all performance metrics, demonstrating superior robustness and generalizability in detecting a wide range of presentation attacks. | Score: 4.81</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Raghavendra Ramachandra, Sushma Venkatesh</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.06103</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Uncertainty-Aware With Adaptive Geometric Correction for Multimodal Land-Cover Classification</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11269698</link>
        <description>We evaluate UAG on the WHU-OPT-SAR and DFC23 datasets, where experimental results demonstrate substantial improvements over state-of-the-art methods. The code will be released at https://github.com/cccwbin/UAGNet | Score: 4.54</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Wenbin Cao;Xu Wang;Yi Xiao;Wenxin Huang;Bihan Wen;Xian Zhong;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11269698</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Soil Moisture Affects Multitemporal InSAR Deformation Monitoring via Dielectric Property Changes</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11262238</link>
        <description>Our findings indicate that dielectric property changes constitute a critical factor in InSAR deformation monitoring that cannot be overlooked. This insight holds significant implications for enhancing the effectiveness of InSAR technology in slope disaster monitoring and early warning systems. | Score: 4.24</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Meng Ao;Xiangben Zhang;Yuan Dai;Lianhuan Wei;Yian Wang;Xiaosong Feng;Shanjun Liu;Mingsheng Liao;Lu Z</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11262238</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Improving Ground Deformation Classification by Integrating InSAR Time Series With Geospatial Information</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11262252</link>
        <description>To fully use the rich information contained in the TS and to exploit the complementary strengths of spatial and temporal data, we propose a dual-branch deep learning (DL) approach that integrates InSAR ground deformation TS with geospatial information for classifying slow-moving ground deformation processes. This work highlights the strength of multimodal data fusion method to classify ground deformation processes, while setting the stage for future research. | Score: 4.20</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Yingbo Dong;Lorenzo Nava;Riccardo Palamà;Oriol Monserrat;Davide Festa;Mario Floris;Ascanio Rosi;Fili</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11262252</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>U-SET: Uncertainty-Aware SAR-to-EO Translation</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</link>
        <description>By leveraging the uncertainty estimation capabilities of deep-learning models, U-SET effectively prioritizes structurally complex and ambiguous regions during training. Comprehensive evaluations on our newly compiled KOMPSAT dataset demonstrate that U-SET achieves state-of-the-art performance, outperforming existing methods across six image quality metrics in both quantitative and qualitative assessments. | Score: 3.56</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Minyoung Jeon;Hyun-Ho Kim;Juheon Park;Doochun Seo;Jaehyup Lee;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Structure-Reduced Dual-Parameter Photonic Crystal Fiber SPR Sensor: Inverse Optimization via Artificial Neural Network and Monte Carlo Hybrid Approach</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11215591</link>
        <description>This work presents an efficient design and optimization framework for dual-parameter photonic crystal fiber (PCF) sensors, integrating structural parameter reduction with artificial intelligence (AI)-based optimization. This design framework not only effectively reduces computational complexity and improves the design efficiency and performance of multiparameter PCF sensors but also provides a general methodological reference for rapid inverse optimization and intelligent integration of other photonic devices. | Score: nan</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Tengfei Xu;Shengli Pu;Siyang Huang;Dan Dong;Xiaolin Lv;Pan Zhou;Hong Zhang;</author>
        <category>Random Discovery</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11215591</guid>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>