<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Daily Paper Digest</title>
        <link>https://github.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage</link>
        <description>Algorithmically selected papers from 20+ journal feeds, focused on RF systems, cultural heritage conservation, and adjacent topics.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:37:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage/main/web/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <generator>Paper Digest Service</generator>
    <item>
        <title>Measurement of Material Volume Fractions in a Microwave Resonant Cavity Sensor Using Convolutional Neural Network</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.13233</link>
        <description>arXiv:2512.13233v1 Announce Type: cross 
Abstract: A non-destructive, real-time method for estimating the volume fraction of a dielectric mixture inside a resonant cavity is presented. The proposed method enables rapid, non-destructive, accurate, low-cost, and real-time estimation of material fractions, illustrating strong potential for sensing applications in microwave material characterization. | Score: 6.88</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Mojtaba Joodaki, Idriz Pelaj</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.13233</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>MVPTransformer: Long-Term Multivariate Time-Series Pattern for Plasma Array-Based Intelligent Protection Against HPM</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</link>
        <description>In this work, we propose a novel time-series modeling approach that integrates multiperspective feature extraction with multihead attention-based information fusion, complemented by an autonomous thinking strategy (ATS). By conducting case studies and comparing our method with three state-of-the-art time-series models, we validate the superior accuracy and generalizability of our proposed approach. | Score: 6.14</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Naixing Feng;Chunzhi Dong;Jianyuan Fu;Fanghua Zheng;Zhixiang Huang;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11126173</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adversarial Attacks Against Deep Learning-Based Radio Frequency Fingerprint Identification</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.12002</link>
        <description>We further used UAP to launch practical attacks. Our experimental evaluation demonstrated that UAP can successfully launch adversarial attacks against the RFFI, achieving a success rate of 81.7% when the adversary almost has no prior knowledge of the victim RFFI systems. | Score: 6.12</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Jie Ma, Junqing Zhang, Guanxiong Shen, Alan Marshall, Chip-Hong Chang</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.12002</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Efficient 3D Surface Super-Resolution via Normal-Based Multimodal Restoration</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11192222</link>
        <description>This paper introduces an efficient multimodal normal-based 3D surface super-resolution (mn3DSSR) framework, designed to address the challenges of microgeometry enhancement and computational overhead. Extensive experiments conducted on seven benchmark datasets across four different 3D data representations demonstrate that mn3DSSR consistently outperforms state-of-the-art super-resolution methods in terms of restoration accuracy with high computational efficiency. | Score: 1.88</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Miaohui Wang;Yunheng Liu;Wuyuan Xie;Boxin Shi;Jianmin Jiang;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11192222</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Epistemoverse: Toward an AI-Driven Knowledge Metaverse for Intellectual Heritage Preservation</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.12201</link>
        <description>Based on these findings, we propose the concept of the Epistemoverse--a metaverse of knowledge where human and machine cognition intersect to preserve, reinterpret, and extend intellectual heritage through AI-driven interaction. This framework positions virtual and immersive environments as new spaces for epistemic exchange, digital heritage, and collaborative creativity. | Score: 0.50</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Predrag K. Nikoli\&#x27;c, Robert Prentner</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.12201</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adaptive FMCW Radar Interference Suppression via Coupled Range-Doppler Unsupervised Sparse Learning and Reconstruction</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</link>
        <description>The simulation and multiple measured experiments demonstrate the proposed method achieves efficient interference suppression performance. Compared to state-of-the-art methods, the time required to process a single frame of measured data is only 0.0872 s, with the best interference suppression performance. | Score: 5.35</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hao Zhang;Shunjun Wei;Rui Min;Xiang Cai;Shuangqiao Li;Jin Li;Mou Wang;Jun Shi;Guolong Cui;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11128914</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>U-SET: Uncertainty-Aware SAR-to-EO Translation</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</link>
        <description>By leveraging the uncertainty estimation capabilities of deep-learning models, U-SET effectively prioritizes structurally complex and ambiguous regions during training. Comprehensive evaluations on our newly compiled KOMPSAT dataset demonstrate that U-SET achieves state-of-the-art performance, outperforming existing methods across six image quality metrics in both quantitative and qualitative assessments. | Score: 3.56</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Minyoung Jeon;Hyun-Ho Kim;Juheon Park;Doochun Seo;Jaehyup Lee;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Regularization-Based Coherence Bias Mitigation for InSAR in Low-Coherence Regions</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11272882</link>
        <description>This study proposes a regularization-based approach to reduce coherence estimation bias, especially in areas with few homogeneous samples. Validated using Monte Carlo simulations and real data from 16 TerraSAR-X images of Shanghai, the proposed approach outperforms conventional techniques, achieving lower residual bias and lower estimation standard deviation (STD) across diverse scenes. | Score: 3.49</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Hongyu Liang;Xin Gao;Xin Li;Lei Zhang;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11272882</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Deep priors for satellite image restoration with accurate uncertainties</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2412.04130</link>
        <description>In this paper, we introduce VBLE-xz, a DR method that solves the inverse problem in the latent space of a variational compressive autoencoder (CAE). The code associated to this paper is available in https://github.com/MaudBqrd/VBLExz. | Score: 3.24</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Biquard Maud, Marie Chabert, Florence Genin, Christophe Latry, Thomas Oberlin</author>
        <category>Adjacent Topics</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2412.04130</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Recurrent Video Masked Autoencoders</title>
        <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.13684</link>
        <description>RVM learns via an asymmetric masked prediction task requiring only a standard pixel reconstruction objective. Finally, we use qualitative visualizations to highlight that RVM learns rich representations of scene semantics, structure, and motion. | Score: nan</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Daniel Zoran, Nikhil Parthasarathy, Yi Yang, Drew A Hudson, Joao Carreira, Andrew Zisserman</author>
        <category>Random Discovery</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.13684</guid>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>