<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Daily Paper Digest</title>
        <link>https://github.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage</link>
        <description>Algorithmically selected papers from 20+ journal feeds, focused on RF systems, cultural heritage conservation, and adjacent opportunities.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 13:37:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ddrizzil/HyperImage/main/web/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <generator>Paper Digest Service</generator>
    <item>
        <title>Snow Depth Estimation Based on STCTNet for Sentinel-1 and Multisource Data</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11227141</link>
        <description>The trained model was then used to predict the average SD for February from 2017 to 2022 at a spatial resolution of 20 m. The application of active microwave data and deep learning techniques in this study provides an approach that improves both the spatial resolution and estimation accuracy of SD. | Score: 5.54</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Qing Cheng;Xinchen Xu;Linwei Yue;Weifeng Hao;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11227141</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Training Signal Optimization for Behavioral Modeling and Digital Predistortion of RF Power Amplifiers</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11184392</link>
        <description>The signal is similar to orthogonal frequency-division multiplexing-based signal standards, facilitating its use in training during the regular operation of the wireless transmitter. Experimental validation of this method is also provided in hardware, with a PA using a 100-MHz bandwidth millimeter wave 5G signal. | Score: 5.27</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Jonathan Guimaraes Ribeiro;Yiyue Jiang;Rahul Mushini;Miriam Leeser;John Dooley;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11184392</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Adaptive Temperature-Driven Ternary Contrastive Autoencoder Framework for Hyperspectral Target Detection</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236413</link>
        <description>Hyperspectral target detection (HTD) is a critical task in remote sensing, where numerous deep learning (DL)-based methods have emerged for their powerful ability to extract hierarchical and discriminative features. Experimental results on four real-world benchmark datasets demonstrate that our approach outperforms state-of-the-art methods in terms of detection performance and efficiency. | Score: 5.24</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Jiaojiao Li;Hangyun Liu;Haitao Xu;Chengyuan Wang;Yunsong Li;Qian Du;</author>
        <category>RF Systems &amp; Nonlinear Phenomena</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236413</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>StylizedGS: Controllable Stylization for 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11143957</link>
        <description>Our method achieves high-quality stylization results characterized by faithful brushstrokes and geometric consistency with flexible controls. Extensive experiments across various scenes and styles demonstrate the effectiveness and efficiency of our method concerning both stylization quality and inference speed. | Score: 0.51</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Dingxi Zhang;Yu-Jie Yuan;Zhuoxun Chen;Fang-Lue Zhang;Zhenliang He;Shiguang Shan;Lin Gao;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11143957</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>A Spike-Driven Transformer Network for Edge Computing-Based Partial Discharge Monitoring Using Ultrahigh Frequency Pulse Signals</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11084948</link>
        <description>To address these issues, this article develops a novel UHF monitoring system by combining a low-noise UHF sensing frontend and a spike-driven Transformer network toward edge computing, enabling a robust, energy-efficient and cost-effective PD recognition. Experimental results demonstrate the highest recognition accuracy, and reductions in computational complexity and energy consumption by 56.25% and 52.0%, respectively. | Score: 5.03</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Changdong Wang;Jingli Yang;Yu’ang Li;Zhou Wang;Huamin Jie;Zhi Zheng;Zhenyu Zhao;Zhou Shu;Yongxin Guo</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11084948</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Despeckling of Synthetic Aperture Radar Images Using Linear–Angular Attention Transformer</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11225891</link>
        <description>In this study, we propose a linear–angular attention transformer network for SAR despeckling. Unlike models that rely on optical images for training and lack domain-specific features for real SAR despeckling, the proposed network is trained directly on SAR images in a self-supervised manner. | Score: 5.02</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Souraja Kundu;M. K. Bhuyan;Karl F. MacDorman;Neeraj Kumar Sharma;Manish Bhatt;</author>
        <category>Cultural Heritage &amp; Conservation Science</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11225891</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>U-SET: Uncertainty-Aware SAR-to-EO Translation</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</link>
        <description>By leveraging the uncertainty estimation capabilities of deep-learning models, U-SET effectively prioritizes structurally complex and ambiguous regions during training. Comprehensive evaluations on our newly compiled KOMPSAT dataset demonstrate that U-SET achieves state-of-the-art performance, outperforming existing methods across six image quality metrics in both quantitative and qualitative assessments. | Score: 3.56</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Minyoung Jeon;Hyun-Ho Kim;Juheon Park;Doochun Seo;Jaehyup Lee;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Opportunities</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11222869</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>A WaveCluster-Based Robust and Fast Multibaseline InSAR Phase Unwrapping Algorithm</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236427</link>
        <description>However, the MBPU methods still cannot effectively balance PU accuracy and efficiency when processing large-size interferograms. Theoretical analysis and experimental results show that this method has more advantages than the existing MBPU methods in efficiency, accuracy, and adaptability to baseline ratios when processing large-size interferograms. | Score: 3.52</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Zhihui Yuan;Zhengguo Wang;Hanwen Yu;Xuemin Xing;Lifan Zhou;Lifu Chen;Junyi Xu;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Opportunities</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11236427</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Multiscale Integration of Spatially Dense InSAR Data and Temporally Intensive GNSS Data Enhances Landslide Displacement Prediction</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11227123</link>
        <description>Due to complex landslide dynamics and the lack of high-quality monitoring data, the timely and accurate prediction of landslide displacement remains challenging. These findings underscore the necessity and feasibility of multisource monitoring data in landslide displacement prediction, providing a robust and scalable framework for landslide disaster prevention. | Score: 3.46</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Qianru Ding;Gang Ma;Chengqian Guo;Hua Chen;Fudong Chi;Wei Zhou;Xiaolin Chang;</author>
        <category>Adjacent Opportunities</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11227123</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Stochastic Channel Models for Satellite Mega-Constellations</title>
        <link>http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11087620</link>
        <description>Global channel parameters such as path loss and channel spread are analysed in terms of the scattering function. The channel statistics and the global channel parameters closely match realistic orbit simulations of the Starlink constellation. | Score: nan</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <author>Brendon McBain;Yi Hong;Emanuele Viterbo;</author>
        <category>Random Discovery</category>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11087620</guid>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>